It's personal.
Vendetta is a action, crime film directed by Jared Cohn.
When his daughter is murdered, William Duncan takes the law into his
own hands, setting out on a quest for retribution.
After killing the street thug responsible for her death, he finds himself in the middle of a war with
the thug's brother, father, and their gang, who are equally hell-bent on getting even.
What ensues is a tense back-and-forth game of vengeance.
By the end, William comes to find that the quest for revenge never has a winner.
William Duncan, played by Clive Standen.
Rory Fetter, played by Theo Rossi.
Dante, played by Thomas Jane.
Detective Chen, played by Kurt Yue.
Donnie Fetter, played by Bruce Willis.
Roach, played by Mike Tyson.
Vendetta is a 2022 American action-thriller revenge film written and directed by Jared Cohn and
starring Clive Standen, Theo Rossi, Mike Tyson, Thomas Jane, and Bruce Willis.
The film was released in limited theaters and on-demand platforms on May 17,
2022, by Redbox Entertainment and Vertical Entertainment.
The tone is intense.